<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Courses>
  <Course Title=".NET 4.0 and Visual Studio 2010">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the enhancements of .NET 4.0 Framework. This includes new features in C# 4.0, LINQ, WCF 4.0, WF 4.0, WPF 4.0, ASP.NET 4.0.</Objective>
    <Link>.NET 4.0 and Visual Studio 2010</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="Windows Communication Foundation 4.0">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand the enhancements made in WCF 4.0 from 3.5 SP1. You will also learn the new features introduced in WCF 4.0.</Objective>
    <Link>Windows Communication Foundation 4.0</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="Silverlight 4.0">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the enhancements of Silverlight 4.0. This includes new features made available in Silverlight 4.0, Business Application Development and changes in RIA.</Objective>
    <Link>Silverlight 4.0</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="Microsoft SharePoint Server 2010">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the enhancements of SharePoint Server 2010. This includes new features like Performance Point Services introduction, BCS, new interface of SPS 2010, Client object Model and many more new features!!</Objective>
    <Link>Microsoft SharePoint Server 2010</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="SQL Server 2008 R2 - Developer Track">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the enhancements of SQL Server 2008 R2. This includes new features in SQL Server 2008 R2. This course is dedicated to SQL Server Devepopers.</Objective>
    <Link>SQL Server 2008 R2</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="Performance Point Servcies">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>The idea behind this course is to make you aware the complete Business Intellegence stack of SharePoint Server 2010. This includes Monitoring capabilities of Performance Point Services by designing DashBoard, KPIs, ScoreCards and also includes the Visio Diagrames for DashBoard Designing!</Objective>
    <Link>Performance Point Services</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="ASP.NET 4.0">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the enhancements of ASP.NET 4.0. This includes new features in ASP.NET 4.0, Introduction to JQuery, new controls and many more !!</Objective>
    <Link>ASP.NET 4.0</Link>
  </Course>
  <Course Title="MOSS 2007">
    <DesignedBy>Pravinkumar R. D.</DesignedBy>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Objective>After completing this course, you will be able understand and implement the Portle for your organization and customers using the rich facilites of MOSS 2007.This course is dedicated to SharePoint Developer (Not for Admins).</Objective>
    <Link>MOSS 2007</Link>
  </Course>
</Courses>